boystown.com.au 2016-12-22

# Privacy | yourtown

## Fundraising Privacy Statement

 **yourtown**  is committed to protecting and securing your privacy and the personal information provided to us.

All personal information collected and held by  **yourtown**  is protected in accordance with Privacy legislation and the Australian Privacy Principles.

 **yourtown**  only collects supporter's personal information for the purposes identified below, and to comply with gaming legislation in the various States and Territories where the Art Union operates. At all times, personal information is collected in a fair and lawful manner.

#### Supporter's right to opt-out

From time to time, promotional offers and special events will be communicated to supporters through direct marketing and other channels. Supporters have the right to opt-out of these communications and can do so through any one of the options listed below.

Phone

| 

1800 500 101 (free call in Australia)

+61 7 3867 1252 (International)  
  
---|---  
  
Fax

| 

Australia 1800 557 067 (free fax in Australia)

+61 7 3367 0642 (International)  
  
Post

| 

 **yourtown** , Reply Paid 2944, Brisbane QLD 4001  
  
Online

| 

Existing supporters can opt-out online. Log in with your account password and follow the 'My Details' link on the top navigation bar  
  
Email

| 

To unsubscribe from the  **yourtown**  email database either click on the link at the bottom of the email you received or send an email to yourtown@yourtown.com.au with the subject 'UNSUBSCRIBE'  
  
#### What kind of personal information is collected?

 **yourtown**  collects and holds the following personal information:

  * Name and address
  * Contact details - phone, fax, mobile, email address
  * Payment details such as credit card number and expiry
  * Date of birth
  * Title
  * Transaction details associated with the purchase of  **yourtown**  tickets and donations

#### Purpose for collection

 **yourtown**  collects supporter's personal information for the primary purpose of fundraising, which includes recording and processing of  **yourtown**  ticket sales and donations. Supporter's personal information is also used for the secondary purpose of marketing, planning, product development and research.

#### Use and Disclosure

Personal information collected by  **yourtown**  will only be used for the purpose it was collected and will not be disclosed to any person, body or agency unless we have your consent or where it is required by law.

 **yourtown**  will not use or disclose or permit the use or disclosure of personal supporter information that could be used to identify an individual supporter in any circumstances except:

  * To ensure the proper functioning of the  **yourtown**  operation
  * Where the personal supporter information is to be used by a retained agent for marketing, planning, product development and research
  * When  **yourtown**  is required by law to disclose the personal supporter information, or
  * When the supporter has consented to the use or disclosure.

#### Cross-Border disclosure

Your personal information is not sent overseas, and is used only by  **yourtown**.

#### Security of Personal Information

 **yourtown**  undertakes to take reasonable steps necessary to ensure that supporter information is secure from any unauthorised access or disclosure.

#### Supported access to personal information

You may ask for access to your information by emailing privacy@yourtown.com.au or by writing to the Chief Executive Officer at:

The Chief Executive Officer  
 **yourtown**  
GPO Box 2469  
Brisbane QLD 4001

An administration fee may be charged to access  **yourtown**  files.

#### How to make a privacy complaint

Inquiries, feedback and complaints concerning privacy can be emailed to privacy@yourtown.com.au or made in writing to:

The Chief Executive Officer  
 **yourtown**  
GPO Box 2469  
Brisbane QLD 4001

#### Our privacy policy

Click here to view our corporate Privacy Policy. You may also request a copy in an alternate format by contacting  **yourtown**  via:

  * Email: privacy@yourtown.com.au
  * Phone: (07) 3368 3399

or by writing to us at the above address.

This Privacy Statement was last updated on 20 March 2014.
